A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051 FA1790
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts, 2007-2017; 3
  - Miami Dade College Foundation Inc. - Miami Book Fair, National Book Foundation and the Porch (2017-54552) (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Miami Dade College Foundation Inc. - Miami Book Fair International (2016-53007) (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Miami Dade College Foundation Inc. - Hialeah Cultural Center, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0384), 2010-2014 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Miami-Dade County - Noches Tropicales (Tropical Nights), Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0344), 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Miami-Dade County Department of Cultural Affairs - Marshall Davis, Knight Art Champion Designation (2017-55391) (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Miami Downtown Development Authority - Summer Shows at the Gusman, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0343), 2010-2013 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Miami Foundation - Deborah Briggs and Johnathan Plutzik, Knight Arts Champion Designation (2017-5537) (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Miami Foundation - Lucas Leyva, Knight Arts Champion Designation (2017-55378) (Box 12, Folder 157)
    Third Horizon Film Festival Fund.
  - Miami Foundation - Dave Barry and Franklin Sirmans, Knight Arts Champion Designation (2017-55384) (Box 12, Folder 158)
    The Havana, Haiti: Two Cultures, One Community by photographer Carl Juste Fund.
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Art Champion Designations (2017-55385) (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Art Student Travel Funds (2017-55305) (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Akron Visual Arts Fund (2017-53937), 2015-2017 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Charlotte Visual Arts Fund (2017-54249), 2014-2017 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Saint Paul Contemporary Dance Fund (2017-54563) (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Akron Youth Performing Arts Fund (2017-54564) (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Akron 2017 (2017-55009), 2014-2017 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Miami 2017 (2017-55017), 2014-2017 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Saint Paul 2017 (2017-55018), 2014-2017 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Detroit 2017 (2017-55154), 2014-2017 (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - Miami Foundation - Charitable Designation, Rosa de la Cruz (2016-52047) (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Akron 2015 (2016-52155), 2013-2017 (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Fund for Independent Cinemas (2016-52193) (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - Miami Foundation - Perez Art Museum Miami Fund for African American Art (2016-53196), 2016-2017 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Saint Paul 2016 (2016-53224), 2013-2017 (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Akron 2016 (2016-53231), 2013-2016 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Detroit 2016 (2016-53232), 2013-2017 (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Northwestern Senior High School Instrument Fund (2016-53584), 2013-2016 (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - Miami Foundation - Charitable Designation, Tarell Alvin McCraney (2016-53592), 2013-2016 (Box 14, Folder 191)
    305/One Festival
  - Miami Foundation - Charitable Designation, Alexandra Codina (2016-53593), 2013-2016 (Box 14, Folder 192)
    Film exploring the stories of marginalized migrant families from Central America.
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Miami 2016 (2016-53605), 2013-2017 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - Miami Foundation - Ing an Die, James McGinn (2016-53617), 2013-2017 (Box 15, Folder 196)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Fund for Contemporary Art in Miami (2015-50412), 2015-2017 (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Art Programming and Acquisition Fund (2015-50413), 2013-2017 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Fund for Independent Cinemas (2015-50425) (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Akron Dance Fund (2015-50430), 2015-2017 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Saint Paul (2015-51625), 2013-2017 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Detroit 2015 (2015-51639), 2013-2017 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Miami 2015, People's Choice Award (2015-51643), 2013-2016 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight American Artists Fellowship Fund (2015-51888), 2013-2016 (Box 16, Folder 207)
  - Miami Foundation - Designated Fund: Knight Akron Theatre Fund (2014-48016), 2012-2017 (Box 16, Folder 210)
  - Miami Foundation - Designated Fund: Knight Akron Artist in Residence Fund (2014-48023), 2012-2017 (Box 16, Folder 211)
  - Miami Foundation - Designated Fund: Knight Akron Youth Performing Arts Fund (2014-48026), 2014-2017 (Box 16, Folder 212)
  - Miami Foundation - Designated Fund: Knight Greater Akron Community Music Fund (2014-48030), 2012-2017 (Box 16, Folder 213)
  - Miami Foundation - Filadelfia Latin American Film Festival (2014-48719), 2012-2014 (Box 16, Folder 214)
  - Miami Foundation - Fresh Produce Records, First Friday Free Concerts (2014-48835), 2012-2014 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - Miami Foundation - Miami Gardens Arts and Humanities Foundation (2014-48976) (Box 17, Folder 217)
  - Miami Foundation - Miami-Dade North Arts and Humanities Foundation (2014-48976), 2011-2015 (Box 17, Folder 218-219)
  - Miami Foundation - Ectotherms by Monica Pena Film Festival Run (2014-49214) (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Miami 2014 (2014-49557), 2014-21016 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Detroit 2014, People's Choice Award (2014-49558), 2012-2015 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Saint Paul 2014 (2014-49559), 2012-2015 (Box 17, Folder 224)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight South Florida Dance Fund (2014-50158), 2012-2017 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Fund for Local Independent Cinemas (2013-46010), 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 230)
  - Miami Foundation - Among Friends, Cesar Trasobares (2013-46549), 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 231)
  - Miami Foundation - Penumbra Strategic Growth Fund (2013-46772), 2011-2017 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Miami Foundation - Springboard for the Arts (2013-46803), 2011-2017 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Miami Foundation - TU Dance Fund (2013-46804), 2011-2017 (Box 18, Folder 234)
  - Miami Foundation - St. Paul Chamber Orchestra (2013-46805), 2011-2017 (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Miami Foundation - The Arts Partnership, Ordway Center for the Arts (2013-46806), 2011-2017 (Box 19, Folder 236)
  - Miami Foundation - Queen City Soup (2013-47021), 2011-2014 (Box 19, Folder 238)
    Soup exchange program in Charlotte, NC.
  - Miami Foundation - Tunnel Cinema, Philadelphia (2013-47079), 2011-2013 (Box 19, Folder 240)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Detroit 2013 (2013-47159), 2011-2015 (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Miami Foundation - Library Acts of Culture (2013-47242), 2011-2013 (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - Miami Foundation - Sculpture Gym (2013-47282), 2011-2013 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Miami Foundation - New Works, North Carolina Dance Theatre Fund (2013-47306), 2011-2017 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Arts Challenge Miami 2013 (2013-47618), 2012-2015 (Box 20, Folder 245)
  - Miami Foundation - Miami City Ballet (2012-0222), 2010-2016 (Box 20, Folder 250)
  - Miami Foundation - Musical Arts Association of Miami (2012-0223), 2012-2016 (Box 20, Folder 251)
  - Miami Foundation - Borscht Corporation (2012-0224), 2011-2017 (Box 20, Folder 252)
  - Miami Foundation - Miami Dade College Foundation (2012-0225), 2010-2016 (Box 21, Folder 253)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Miami Student Travel Fund (2012-0226), 2011-2016 (Box 21, Folder 254)
  - Miami Foundation - Florida International University Foundation (2012-0227), 2011-2014 (Box 21, Folder 255)
  - Miami Foundation - D.A.S.H. Design Student Scholarship (2012-0140), 2011-2012 (Box 21, Folder 256)
  - Miami International Airport, Division of Fine Arts and Cultural Affairs - World Music Performances (2012-0385), 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 263)
  - Miami Light Project - Feasibility Study and Planning (2017-54480), 2015-2017 (Box 22, Folder 264)
  - Miami Light Project - Put A Beard On Miami (2016-53618) (Box 22, Folder 265)
    To host the Philadelphia-based cabaret company, The Bearded Ladies, in Miami for a two-week cabaret residency including live performances, performance workshops, stilt-walking, queer theater-making, and parades for Miami artists and community.
  - Miami Light Project - Complex Movements Project (2014-49940), 2014-2016 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    "Beware the Dandelions" by Complex Movements.
  - Miami Lyric Opera Inc. - Classical Opera Staging for Young Talents, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0346), 2010-2012 (Box 22, Folder 267)
  - Miami Museum of Science - Learning Center and the Patricia and Phillip Frost Museum of Science (2011-0378), 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 269-270)
  - Miami Music Project - Parker Thomson Student Conducting Fellowship (2017-55292) (Box 23, Folder 271)
  - Miami Theatre Center - Black Box Theater (2012-0397), 2012-2016 (Box 23, Folder 273)
  - Michael Bell - Miami-Dade Region of the Scholastic Writing Awards Program, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0266), 2007-2013 (Box 23, Folder 274)
  - Mideastern Dance Exchange - Havana Habibi, Tiffany Madera (2016-52570), 2013-2016 (Box 23, Folder 279)
  - Minneapolis Society of Fine Arts - Open Source Storytelling for Museums (2017-54171) (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Minnesota State Fair Foundation - Public Arts at the State Fair (2012-0363), 2010-2013 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Mint Museum of Art Inc. - Interactive Staircase (2017-54066) (Box 25, Folder 299)
  - Mint Museum of Art Inc. - State of the Art (2016-52851) (Box 25, Folder 300)
  - MoBallet - Legacy of Black Ballet in Philadelphia (2016-52175) (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Monica Pena - Observations on the Feeling (2014-49886), 2012-2015 (Box 25, Folder 307)
  - Movimiento de Arte y Cultura Latino Americana de San Jose - DZine at San Jose Airport, Carlos Rolon (2017-54983) (Box 25, Folder 310)
  - Movimiento de Arte y Cultura Latino Americana de San Jose - Reaching Silicon Valley through Cultura (2016-53355) (Box 25, Folder 311)
  - Murray Dranoff Foundation, Inc. - Mayor Carlos Gimenez, Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55376) (Box 26, Folder 319)
  - Museum of Arts and Sciences, Inc. - Macon Fulldome Film Festival (2017-54063) (Box 26, Folder 320)
  - Museum of Arts and Sciences, Inc. - Emerging Artists Exhibition (2017-55005) (Box 26, Folder 321)
  - Museum of Arts and Sciences, Inc. - Art on the Trail (2016-52700), 2016-2017 (Box 26, Folder 322)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art - Coyote Treasure Hunt (2017-54169) (Box 26, Folder 323)
  - Naatak - Vrindavan and 2016 Main Stage Production (2015-50846), 2015-2016 (Box 26, Folder 326)
  - Naatak - 2017 Musical (2016-52678) (Box 26, Folder 327)
  - Naatak - Amaa Vasya (2013-46786), 2012-2014 (Box 26, Folder 328)
  - Name Publications - Miami Women Artists Books, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-1740), 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 329)
  - National Association of Latino Arts and Culture - NALAC Regional Workshops: Miami and Detroit (2014-48117) (Box 28, Folder 342)
  - National Foundation for Advancement in the Arts - #Josh at YoungArts (2017-54326) (Box 28, Folder 349)
  - National Foundation for Advancement in the Arts - Sarah Arison, Knight Art Champion Designation 2017 (2017-55369) (Box 28, Folder 350)
  - National Tropical Botanical Garden - Mark Dion, Digital Garden at the Kampong (2015-51555), 2012-2016 (Box 29, Folder 364)
  - Nautilus Musical Theater - Dead Man Walking (2012-0243) (Box 29, Folder 366)
  - Neos Dance Theatre - Multimedia and Dance (2014-49263) (Box 30, Folder 369)
  - New World Symphony - National Instrumentalist Mentoring and Audition Training Convening (2016-52998) (Box 32, Folder 400)
  - New World Symphony - Video Commission (2016-53315), 2014-2016 (Box 32, Folder 401)
  - New World Symphony - Crowdsource Symphony, Miami (2016-53056), 2014-2016 (Box 32, Folder 402)
  - Nichole Canuso Dance Company - Invisible Cities, Italo Calvino, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0061), 2009-2014 (Box 33, Folder 422)
  - Nonprofit Finance Fund - ArtPlace (2011-0222), 2009-2013 (Box 33, Folder 424)
  - Nova Southeastern University - CoBrA: Multidisciplinary Response to International Collaboration, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0347), 2011-2015 (Box 35, Folder 443-444)
  - Oneaka Dance Company - Dances of the Soul (2014-49297), 2012-2014 (Box 36, Folder 452)
  - One Voice Chorus - Codebreaker (2016-52694) (Box 36, Folder 455)
    Production of Codebreaker, a piece that deals with themes of identity and acceptance in the LGBTQ community, performed by One Voice Chorus and Nashville Harmony Chorus in Charlotte.
  - On Q Performing Arts - Miles and Coltrane: Blue (.) by Concrete Generation (2016-52704) (Box 37, Folder 467)
  - Open Lab, Miami - Local Film Community Gathering, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0390), 2011-2016 (Box 37, Folder 470)
  - Opera Carolina - Opera Unlimited (2016-52679) (Box 38, Folder 472)
  - Opera Cultura - Engaging New Audiences (2017-54782) (Box 38, Folder 473)
  - Opera Carolina - Street Opera (2014-49243), 2014-2015 (Box 38, Folder 474)
  - Opera Cultura - Bless Me, Ultima (2014-49121), 2012-2014 (Box 38, Folder 475)
  - Opera Philadelphia - Festival O: Invigorating Art, Consumers and Civic Life (2015-51628), 2015-2017 (Box 38, Folder 476)
  - Opera Cultura - Bless Me, Ultima (2015-50742) (Box 38, Folder 479)
  - Otis Redding Foundation - Growing Macon's Young Musicians (2017-54753) (Box 38, Folder 482)
  - Painted Bride Art Center - Secret Show (2016-52620) (Box 39, Folder 485)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - Church Theater Space (2012-0086), 2009-2015 (Box 39, Folder 489)
  - Preserving, Archiving, and Teaching Hiphop Inc. (PATH) - The Last Jimmy: A Hip-Hop Musical (2016-52367), 2014-2016 (Box 39, Folder 490)
  - Pennsylvania Ballet Association - Jerome Robbins Match for "Canvas" (2014-49286) (Box 40, Folder 499)
  - Performing Arts Center Trust, Inc. - "Ing an Die" featuring James McGinn (2017-54967) (Box 40, Folder 504)
  - Peter London Global Dance Theater - South Florida Dance Support, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0349), 2011-2014 (Box 41, Folder 509)
  - Philadelphia Dance Company - Straight Outta Philly (2016-52635), 2016-2017 (Box 41, Folder 514)
  - Philadelphia Film Society - At Home on the Big Screen (2012-3436), 2011-2014 (Box 41, Folder 515)
  - Philadelphia Film Society - Short Film Competition, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0063), 2009-2012 (Box 41, Folder 516)
  - Philadelphia Fringe Festival - African American Engagement at the 2016 Festival (2016-52666) (Box 42, Folder 520)
  - Philadelphia Gay Men's Chorus (PGMC) - When I Knew (2013-46344), 2012-2014 (Box 42, Folder 521)
  - Philadelphia Mural Arts Advocates - Open Source (2015-50544) (Box 42, Folder 523)
    Public artworks that explore and illuminate the city's diverse urban identity.
  - Philadelphia Mural Arts Advocates - Operation Food for Thought (2012-3269), 2011-2016 (Box 42, Folder 524)
  - Philadelphia Mural Arts Advocates - Favelas to Philly, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0065), 2009-2012 (Box 42, Folder 525)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Inside Out, Philadelphia (2016-53459), 2016-2017 (Box 42, Folder 526)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Inside Out, Philadelphia (2015-50823), 2014-2016 (Box 42, Folder 527)
  - The Philadelphia Orchestra Association - Voice of Philadelphia (2016-53311) (Box 43, Folder 528)
  - Philadelphia Parks and Recreation's Performing Arts Office - After-School Engagement (REACH) (2014-48735), 2011-2015 (Box 43, Folder 529)
  - Philadelphia Photo Arts Center - Curatorial Risk and Audience Engagement (2017-54796) (Box 43, Folder 530)
  - Philadelphia Theatre Company - The Pipeline Project (2012-2498), 2010-2014 (Box 43, Folder 536)
  - Philadelphia Youth Poetry Movement - Youth Poetry Movement, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0069), 2009-2013 (Box 43, Folder 537)
  - Phi Clef Club of Jazz and Performing Arts Inc. - Preservation Jazz Series (2014-50248), 2014-2015 (Box 44, Folder 548)
  - Phillips Performing Arts Foundation, Inc. - Summer Camp (2015-50628), 2013-2016 (Box 44, Folder 550)
  - Phillips Performing Arts Foundation, Inc. - Summer Camp (2016-52698), 2013-2016 (Box 44, Folder 551)
  - The Philly Pigeon - Philadelphia Poetry Slam, Jacob Winterstein (2012-3058), 2011-2014 (Box 44, Folder 552)
  - Philly Youth Poetry Movement - Brave New Voices International Youth Poetry Festival (2013-46457), 2011-2013 (Box 44, Folder 553)
  - Pig Iron Theatre Company - Dr. Dog and Pig Iron: Leavers and Takers, the Concert Spectacle (2012-3305), 2011-2014 (Box 44, Folder 555)
  - Play On, Philly! - Fostering Artistic Excellence (2017-54815) (Box 44, Folder 558)
  - Play On, Philly! - POP Academy (2015-50608), 2012-2016 (Box 44, Folder 559)
  - Play On, Philly! - Music Skills (2012-3437), 2012-2016 (Box 44, Folder 560)
  - Poetic Peace Arts - Spoken Word Events (2015-50799), 2013-2016 (Box 45, Folder 563)
  - Public Interest - Vitality of Cultural Life (2011-0187), 2010-2012 (Box 47, Folder 601)
  - Que-OS - BOOM Charlotte Fringe Festival (2017-54797) (Box 48, Folder 614)
  - Que-OS - BOOM Festival 2017 (2016-52627) (Box 48, Folder 615)
  - Rakontur Short Form LLC - Miami Beach Documentary Film (2015-50615), 2013-2015 (Box 48, Folder 618)
  - Reading Queer - Center for LGBT Literature (2012-0392), 2011-2016 (Box 48, Folder 621)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Sphinx, Mosiac Theater, Michigan Opera, and Detroit School of Arts (2012-0220), 2012-2016 (Box 49, Folder 634)
  - The Rhythm Foundation - Big Night in Little Haiti, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0273), 2008-2012 (Box 49, Folder 637)
  - Rockefeller Philanthropy Advisors - ArtPlace America (2015-51566), 2015-2016 (Box 50, Folder 646)
  - Rockefeller Philanthropy Advisors - ArtPlace (2013-42801), 2012-2014 (Box 50, Folder 647)
  - Roofless Records - Worthy Spectacles and Obsolete Mediums, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0350), 2010-2013 (Box 50, Folder 648)
  - Rosa Herrera - Herrera Dance Theatre (2012-0020), 2011-2014 (Box 50, Folder 649)
  - Sandra and Leon Levine Jewish Community Center Inc. - Charlotte Jewish Film Festival Young Adult Engagement Project (2016-52681), 2016-2017 (Box 52, Folder 667)
  - San Jose Center for Poetry and Literature - Second Annual San Jose Poetry Festival (2016-52364) (Box 52, Folder 671)
  - San Jose Institute of Contemporary Art - Sandbox Projects (2017-55011) (Box 52, Folder 675)
  - San Jose Jazz - KSJZ Neighborhood-Based Pirate Radio (2016-52730) (Box 52, Folder 676)
  - San Jose Jazz - Progressions (2015-50818) (Box 52, Folder 677)
  - San Jose Institute of Contemporary Art - Jim Campbell Exhibition (2015-50822) (Box 52, Folder 678)
  - San Jose Museum of Art Association - The Propeller Group (2017-54953) (Box 52, Folder 679)
  - San Jose Museum of Art Association - Your Mind, This Moment: Art and the Practice of Attention (2016-52646) (Box 52, Folder 680)
  - San Jose Stage Company - The Memory Stick (2016-52693) (Box 53, Folder 684)
  - San Jose Taiko Group - Japantown Immersive (2016-52611), 2013-2016 (Box 53, Folder 685)
  - Savvy Organization, Inc. - Charlotte New Music Festival (2015-50783) (Box 53, Folder 690)
  - School of Arts and Culture at the Mexican Heritage Plaza - Community Engagement Program and Multicultural Arts Leadership Institute (2017-54757) (Box 53, Folder 691)
  - School of Arts and Culture at the Mexican Heritage Plaza - Multicultural Arts Leadership Insititute (2016-52676) (Box 53, Folder 692)
  - School of Arts and Culture at the Mexican Heritage Plaza - Community Engagement Project (2016-52677) (Box 53, Folder 694)
  - Schott Foundation for Public Education - 25th Anniversary Support (2017-54303) (Box 54, Folder 698)
  - Sean Stoops - 3D Storytelling (2012-0088), 2011-2015 (Box 54, Folder 700)
    A series of outdoor video art events screened on local buildings.
  - Seeing Things Gallery - Print Exchange Program (2014-49178), 2012-2014 (Box 54, Folder 701)
  - Silicon Valley Creates - Anne and Mark's Art Party (2016-52663), 2014-2016 (Box 55, Folder 716)
  - The Soap Factory - Hand-in-Glove Conference (2015-50891) (Box 55, Folder 724)
  - SoundX LLC - Corner Concerts II (2016-52632), 2013-2016 (Box 56, Folder 737)
  - SoundX LLC - Corner Concerts (2015-50612), 2012-2015 (Box 56, Folder 738)
  - South Street Headhouse District - Pop-Up and Street Events (2012-3095), 2010-2014 (Box 58, Folder 757)
  - Springboard for the Arts - World-Premiere Screening, Open Book Minneapolis (2012-0255), 2010-2012 (Box 58, Folder 761)
  - Struti, The India Music and Dance Society - Bringing Indian Music with an Edge to Philadelphia (2012-2435), 2011-2015 (Box 59, Folder 770)
  - Sundance Institute - Sundance Labs Initiative 2.0 (2017-54060), 2015-2017 (Box 61, Folder 795)
  - Sundance Institute - Sundance Labs Initiative (2014-49743), 2011-2016 (Box 61, Folder 796)
  - Sweat Records - Sweat's Record Store Day Get-Down (2016-52279), 2013-2016 (Box 61, Folder 800)
  - Sweat Records - All-Ages Concerts (2012-0394), 2011-2014 (Box 61, Folder 801)
  - Sweat Records - Miami's Indie Epicenter (2009-0189), 2009-2012 (Box 61, Folder 802)
  - Swim Pony Performing Arts - The End 2.0 (2017-55022) (Box 61, Folder 803)
    A month-long transmedia performance/game experienced via text message.
  - Swim Pony Performing Arts - The End (2015-51499), 2013-2015 (Box 61, Folder 804)
  - Symphony Silicon Valley - Digital Marketing for Younger Audiences (2016-52719) (Box 61, Folder 805)
  - Tabard Theatre Company - 10 in 10 (2014-49292), 2014-2015 (Box 62, Folder 807)
  - Taller Puertorriqueño - Yo Soy Oro (I Am Gold): Phase One (2016-52762) (Box 62, Folder 810)
  - Taproot - Theatrical Productions (2015-50629) (Box 62, Folder 811)
  - Teatro Avante Inc. - Latino Theater, Playwrights, Directors, and Artists in the Miami-based International Hispanic Theatre Festival, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0351), 2011-2012 (Box 62, Folder 818)
  - Taller Puertorriqueño - Heart of Latino Philadelphia, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0071), 2011-2012 (Box 62, Folder 819)
  - Taller Puertorriqueño - Heart of Latino Philadelphia, Knight Arts Challenge: Videos of Cafe under the Stars Events (2011-0071), 2012 (Box 62, Folder 819)
  - Teatro Vision de San Jose - Chicano Play, Teatro Visión (2016-52600) (Box 63, Folder 820)
  - Tectonic Theater Project, Inc. - Carmen (2014-49982) (Box 63, Folder 836)
    Moises Kaufman's Afro-Cuban adaptation of Bizet's opera, Carmen.
  - Temple University - Arts Wide-Open in North Philadelphia, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0072), 2009-2013 (Box 64, Folder 841)
  - theartblog.org - The Artist and Social Responsibility (2013-47080), 2013-2014 (Box 64, Folder 844)
  - Theatre Alliance of Greater Philadelphia - Fill in the Blanks with Theatre, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0074), 2009-2012 (Box 64, Folder 845)
  - Theater Mu, Inc. - Taiko Drums (2013-46757), 2011-2013 (Box 64, Folder 846)
  - Three Aksha - Choreography for Natyashastra (2016-52699) (Box 64, Folder 849)
  - Thomas Armour Youth Ballet - Lourdes Lopez, Knight Art Champion (2017-55379) (Box 64, Folder 852)
  - Thought Loom - Seasonal Performances (2012-0400), 2011-2015 (Box 65, Folder 853)
  - Tigertail Productions - Is Paris Burning? (2011-0353), 2010-2014 (Box 65, Folder 857)
  - Tiny Dynamite Productions - A Play, a Pie, and a Pint, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0075), 2008-2012 (Box 65, Folder 859)
  - Tosco Music Parties, Inc. - Parties for Seniors (2016-52702) (Box 65, Folder 863)